The Sound Asleep Air Mattress is perfect for people who need extra comfort. It’s extremely durable and utilizes a Comfortcoil technology for maximum comfort. This is one of the absolute best that you can find on the market. It’s perfect for guests, and some customers even use this as an alternative to regular blow-up beds.

The bottom of it is coated with “Sure Grip,” a layer of anti-slip rubber that sticks to the floor, and makes them more sturdy and secure during the night. The Sure Grip material also helps make this safer for children who like to move around. That is why we like Sound Asleep Air Mattress so much, it's a safe and reliable option for buyers, and not to mention very cheap for its quality. 

In addition to Sound Asleep Air Mattress being awesome, it’s completely waterproof, durable, and comes with a one-year warranty – or money back guarantees. The air pump is fast and efficient, just plug it into an electrical outlet, flip the on switch, and watch as it immediately inflates in front of your eyes. The air pump can increase it in less than 4 minutes. It can also deflate it with ease.